merakyahoga.com 2016-04-25

# Mera Kya Hoga- Get Right Advice, Absolutely Free!

* ### DEFINITIONS:-

(a)  **USER :-**   USER includes "any person, professional, expert, agency, vendor, consultant, but not limited to the definition of USER defined here. Any person who has attained the age of 18 years falls within the purview of the USER.

(b)   **EXPERT :-**   EXPERT refers to a Professional, Expert, Consultant, pioneer in his/her core area of Profession.

(c)   **AGENCY, VENDORS :-**   AGENCY and VENDORS includes all kinds of agencies, businesses, outlets, Agents, shops, Malls but not limited to the definition defined here.

(d)   **MERAKYAHOGA.COM :-**   MERAKYAHOGA.COM includes its Companies, sister concerns, affiliates, representatives, agents, licensors, divisions.

(e)   **SERVICE and SITES :-**   SERVICE includes the service of Experts, Professionals, Agencies and SITES includes all the sites which are displayed on the portal of MERAKYAHOGA.

At Merakyahoga.com, we are committed to protecting the privacy and confidentiality of all Personal Information that the USER may share with us. We understand the importance of the information the USER entrusts to us at all times.

This Privacy Policy describes our best practices concerning the information collected by the Merakyahoga.comthrough the use of:-

* ### WEBSITE

MERAKYAHOGA.COM mobile applications

Merakyahoga.com will continue to evaluate and update this Privacy Policy against new technologies, business practices, users, experts, agency needs, and may make changes to the Privacy Policy accordingly. All users, experts, agencies, vendors are advised to check this page periodically and at regular intervals for latest updates. If Merakyahoga.com makes any materialchanges to this Privacy Policy, we will post the updated Privacy Policy here, along with its effective date. USER’s continued use of the Services and site after our posting of changes to this Privacy Policy means that USERagrees to be bound by such changes. AGE ENTRY

* ### AGE ENTRY AND VERIFICATION

The Services and site are not intended for USERS under the age of 18 years. Merakyahoga.com does not knowingly collect any personal information, data, and recordsfor children under 18 or minors. If any point of time it comes to ourknowledge and information that a person submitting information is under 18, we will attempt to delete the information/ accountin the first instance. Further USER hereby represents that user has attained the age of at least 18 years.

* ### USER, EXPERT, VENDOR, AGENCY ANDCONSULTANT’S INFORMATION

USER’S use of the Services may require initial registration at Merakyahoga.com, in which case Merakyahoga.comwill ask USER to provide certain personal information, background, email address, contact details username, and password.

We have kept the registration procedure simple and easy for our USERS. To protect USER’s privacy and security, we also take reasonable steps to verify USER identity before granting access or making corrections.

A user may also decide to provide with some optional demographic information to enhance USER profile and background, viz.Country of residence, practice area, home address, education, interests, awards achieved, and communications preferences.

* ### TIME DURATION, FOR STORAGE OF INFORMATION COLLECTED

MERAKYAHOGA.COM retains and stores the information collected about and from the USER for as long as necessary to fulfil a business purpose or need of the USER and to comply with a legal request/ mandate made by any official authorities or offices.

* ### Information Collected When User uses The Services and Site:

When USER uses the Services and site, Merakyahoga.comautomatically collects and stores crucial and relevant information/data about user computer or device and USER’s activities, including:

(1)  IP address of USER computer or any other using device.

(2)  Unique mobile device identifier, Country Code, Country Name, City Area.

(3)  Type of device, Mobile device ID number, Windows Type, web browser and operating system

(4)  USER preferences and settings (time zone, language, etc.)

(5)  Any other relevant technical information, but not limited to listed above.

* ### USAGE AND SHARING OF INFORMATION COLLECTED BY MERAKYAHOGA.COM

Merakyahoga.comshall use the information/ datacollected from and about USER for the following purposes, but not limited to, listed as under:

(a)  Respond to USER queries with the best possible solutionsand optimum search results.

(b)  Providing USERS with customer and Tech support.

(c)  Administer our Services and site, diagnose technical and other software problems.

(d)  Sending relevant communications requested or demanded by USER.

(e)  Any other relevant information beyond mentioned above.

Merakyahoga.comwill not share any personal information collected about the USER with any third party/ies for their own marketing purposes without user consent. The shared/ collected information will be used in the following ways:

A)  **USER’s Consent :-**  If we have USER’s consent or deemed consent to do so, we will share the information as and where we feel it is required.

B)  **Research, Marketing and Strategic Analysis :-**  Personal Information of the USER will be kept confidential and will be used for our research, marketing, and strategic client analysis objectives and other internal business purposes only.

C)  **Agencies, Consultants, Subcontractors, Experts and Business partners :-**  We may share Users’ data with our service providers. We have contracts with our service providers that prohibit them from sharing the information about the USER that they collect for not using it for other purposes.

D)  **Prevention of Acts like Fraud or Misrepresentation :-**  MERAKYAHOGA.COM may disclose the personal information collected about the users/ experts when it comes to the knowledge that disclosure is necessary to investigate, prevent, or respond to suspected illegal or fraudulent activity/ies or to protect the safety, rights, or property of us, our users, or others.

E)  **Enforcement of Law :-**  If at any point of time we are requested by the government authorities or officials, such as Law Enforcement Authorities, Legitimate Courts, or Regulators, Regulating Authorities or otherwise to comply with the law, MERAKYAHOGA.COM may disclose any part of information/ full information which we have about our USERS. Our Group may disclose information collected about you in order to exercise or protect legal rights or defend against legal claims.

F)  **Transfer, Sale, Merger of Business or Companies :-**  MERAKYAHOGA.COM may transfer USER personal information to a third party if we or any of our GROUPis involved in a corporate restructuring, Merger, sale of any Business.

G)  **Any other Purpose :-**  We may share the information of the USER for any other purpose other than mentioned above but that will be in the interest of the USER and within the parameters of the Terms of Service, User Agreement and Privacy Policy.

* ### UPDATING, AMENDING THE INFORMATION OF USER

If USER likes to change, alter, amend or delete personal information collected from Merakyahoga.com, or if USER wishes to permanently deactivate the account at any point of time, the same can be done by following the "Account settings".

* ### SECRECY/ CONFIDENTIALITY OF INFORMATION

Merakyahoga.com takes the security and confidentiality of USER’s personal information seriously and uses appropriate technical measures to protect USER’spersonal information against unauthorized or unlawful processing and against accidental loss, destruction or damage. However, despite that Merakyahoga.com will not be held liable for any leakage of information, data through unfair means and practices.
